<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Topic>
	<Food>
		<Algeria>
			<Couscous>Often considered the national dish of Algeria, Couscous is a perfect complement to any meal. This dish is composed of small pellets of steamed semolina topped with meat, vegetables, and various spices. In Algeria, the most popular meat and vegetable accompaniments for this meal include chicken, carrots and chickpeas. Although a rather simple dish, Couscous offers considerable freedom in its selection of ingredients.
			</Couscous>
		</Algeria>

		<Australia>
			<Meat surname="Pie">An Australian meat pie is a hand-sized meat pie containing diced or minced meat and gravy, sometimes with onion, mushrooms, or cheese and often consumed as a takeaway food snack. The meat pie is considered iconic in Australia and also in New Zealand, which regards pie as a part of the country's cuisine, as it forms part of the New Zealand national identity.
			</Meat>
		</Australia>

		<Brazil>
			<Brigadeiro>The brigadeiro is a common Brazilian delicacy, created in the 40's. The brigadeiro is made from condensed milk, cocoa powder, butter and chocolate sprinkles to cover the outside layer. The information regarding when and where the brigadeiro was invented is uncertain, but many believe it's from São Paulo. One fact about brigadeiro is that you can't eat just one!
			</Brigadeiro>
		</Brazil>

		<Canada>
			<Poutine>It  is a Canadian dish originating from the province of Quebec, originally made with French fries and cheese curds topped with a brown gravy. The dish emerged in the late 1950s, but for most of its existence, poutine was negatively perceived and mocked, which is in drastic contrast with its later popularity. In the past, poutine was even used as a means of stigmatization against the Quebec society. Today, poutine is celebrated both within Quebec and throughout the rest of Canada. 
			</Poutine>
		</Canada>

		<China>
			<Lo surname="Mein">It is a Chinese dish with wheat flour noodles. It often contains vegetables and some type of meat or seafood, usually beef, chicken, pork, shrimp or wontons. It can also be eaten with just vegetables.
			</Lo>
		</China>

		<Egypt>
			<Konafah>Konafah is an Egyptian sweet made of a very thin noodle-like pastry. Its origins are very mysterious, its presence has been recorded in Arab medieval cookbooks in both Egypt and the Levant and Turkey. Konafah is made by drizzling long rows of the thin noodles in their liquid state on a hot plate until they become dry and more rigid. The now-rigid noodles are then mixed with butter or oil and wrapped around a filling made out of nuts, whipped cream or both. It is baked and presented with a fruit syrup on top.
			</Konafah>
		</Egypt>

		<England>
			<Fish surname="and Chips">Fish and chips is a hot dish of English origin consisting of fried battered fish and hot potato chips. It is a common take-away food and an early example of culinary fusion. Fish and chips first appeared in the 1860s; by 1910 there were more than 25,000 fish and chip shops across the UK, and by the 1930s there were over 35,000.It was formerly sold in newspaper pages.
			</Fish>
		</England>

		<France>
			<Macaron>A Macaron is a sweet meringue-based confection made with egg white, icing sugar, granulated sugar, almond powder or ground almond, and food coloring. The macaron commonly consists of a ganache, buttercream or jam filling sandwiched between two cookies. The name is derived from the Italian word macarone
			</Macaron>
		</France>

		<Germany>
			<Brezel>Brezel are soft, white pretzels made from flour water and yeast and sprinkled with salt (and sometimes different seeds). It's great to eat as a side dish or snack. They’re in every bakery and on street stands, sold plain, sliced and buttered (butterbrezel) or with slices of cold meats or cheese.
			</Brezel>
		</Germany>

		<Italy>
			<Pizza>Okay, this one you might have already eaten. But did you know that the term pizza was first recorded in the 10th century, in a Latin manuscript from Gaeta in Southern Lazio? It's believed that initially, its flavor was only tomatoe sauce and nothing else. Modern pizza was invented in Naples, Campania, Southern Italy, and the dish and its variants have since become popular and common in many areas of the world.
			</Pizza>
		</Italy>

		<Portugal>
			<Alheira>The alheira is a type of Portuguese sausage, made with meats other than pork (usually veal, duck, chicken, quail or rabbit) and bread. Although alheira derives from "alho" (garlic) and was once used to describe any sausage seasoned with it, not all present-day alheiras contain garlic, although it is still a common ingredient.
			</Alheira>
		</Portugal>

		<Spain>
			<Pisto>This vegetarian top Spanish dish is eaten as a tapa, appetiser, a side dish to meats, or even as a meal with a fried egg on top or chorizo. It's a Spanish ratatouille of tomatoes, peppers, zucchini, onions, garlic, and of course, olive oil. You can find it in restaurants around Spain, and especially in the towns across the plains of La Mancha, south of Madrid.
			</Pisto>
		</Spain>

		<USA>
			<Burguer>There have been many claims about the origin of the hamburger, but the origins remain unclear. The popular book "The Art of Cookery made Plain and Easy" by Hannah Glasse included a recipe in 1758 as "Hamburgh sausage", which suggested to serve it "roasted with toasted bread under it". A similar snack was also popular in Hamburg by the name "Rundstück warm" ("bread roll warm") in 1869 or earlier, and supposedly eaten by many emigrants on their way to America. Although its uncertain origin, one thing  is certain: today this is one of the most eaten dishes in the world!
			</Burguer>
		</USA>

		<Russia>
			<Stroganoff>Strips of beef sauteed in a sauce of butter, white wine, sour cream, mustard and onions. Eaten either straight or poured over rice or noodles. Wholesome and hearty. Although it derives its name from the influential Stroganov family in Russia and you can find variants in fancy restaurants, it still tastes like a no-fuss dish you’d make on a Sunday evening.
			</Stroganoff>
		</Russia>
	</Food>

	<Flag>
		<Algeria>The national flag of Algeria consists of two equal vertical bars, green and white, charged in the center with a red star and crescent. The flag was adopted on 3 July 1962.
		</Algeria>

		<Australia>The flag of Australia is a defaced Blue Ensign: a blue field with the Union Jack in the canton (upper hoist quarter), and a large white seven-pointed star known as the Commonwealth Star in the lower hoist quarter. The fly contains a representation of the Southern Cross constellation, made up of five white stars – one small five-pointed star and four, larger, seven-pointed stars.
		</Australia>

		<Brazil>The flag of Brazil is a blue disc depicting a starry sky (which includes the Southern Cross constellation) spanned by a curved band inscribed with the national motto "Ordem e Progresso" ("Order and Progress"), within a yellow rhombus, on a green field. Brazil officially adopted this design for its national flag on 1889 — four days after the Proclamation of the Republic, to replace the flag of the Empire of Brazil.
		</Brazil>

		<Canada>The flag of Canada, or unofficially as the Maple Leaf, is a national flag consisting of a red field with a white square at its centre in the ratio of 1:2:1, in the middle of which is featured a stylized, red, 11-pointed maple leaf charged in the centre. It is the first specified by law for use as the country's national flag, on 1965.
		</Canada>

		<China>The flag of the People's Republic of China, also known as the Five-star Red Flag, is a red field charged in the canton with five golden stars. The design features one large star, with four smaller stars in a semicircle set off towards the fly (the side farthest from the flag pole). The red represents the communist revolution; the five stars and their relationship represent the unity of the Chinese people under the leadership of the Communist Party of China (CPC). The first flag was hoisted on 1949, at a ceremony announcing the founding of the People's Republic.
		</China>

		<Egypt>The flag of Egypt is a tricolour consisting of the three equal horizontal red, white, and black bands of the Arab Liberation flag dating back to the Egyptian Revolution of 1952. The flag bears Egypt's national emblem, the Eagle of Saladin centered in the white band.
		</Egypt>

		<England>The flag of England is derived from St George's Cross. The association of the red cross as an emblem of England can be traced back to the Middle Ages, and it was used as a component in the design of the Union Flag in 1606. Since the 1990s it has been in increasingly wide use, particularly at national sporting events.
		</England>

		<France>The flag of France is a tricolour flag featuring three vertical bands coloured blue, white, and red. It is known to English speakers as the French Tricolour or simply the Tricolour. The Tricolour has become one of the most influential flags in history, with its three-color scheme being copied by many other nations, both in Europe and the rest of the world.
		</France>

		<Germany>The flag of Germany is a tricolour consisting of three equal horizontal bands displaying the national colours of Germany: black, red, and gold (not yellow). The flag was first adopted as the national flag of modern Germany in 1919, during the short-lived Weimar Republic to 1933.
		</Germany>

		<Italy>The flag of Italy is a tricolour featuring three equally-sized vertical pales of green, white and red. Its current form has been in use since 1946. Some have attributed particular values to the colours, and a common interpretation is that the green represents the country's plains and the hills; white, the snow-capped Alps; and red, blood spilt in the Wars of Italian Independence and Unification.
		</Italy>

		<Portugal>The flag of Portugal is a rectangular bicolour with a field unevenly divided into green on the hoist, and red on the fly. The lesser version of the national coat of arms (i.e. armillary sphere and Portuguese shield) is centered over the colour boundary at equal distance from the upper and lower edges. On 1911, less than a year after the downfall of the constitutional monarchy, this design was officially adopted for the new national flag of the First Portuguese Republic. 
		</Portugal>

		<Spain>The flag of Spain, as it is defined in the Spanish Constitution of 1978, consists of three horizontal stripes: red, yellow and red, the yellow stripe being twice the size of each red stripe. The coat of arms of Spain (in the left side of the flag) symbolizes the country and the nation; the old kingdoms of Spain, the Royal Crown, the Imperial Crown, the Constitutional monarchy, the Spanish national motto: Plus Ultra, and the Pillars of Hercules.
		</Spain> 

		<USA>The flag consists of thirteen equal horizontal stripes of red alternating with white, with a blue rectangle in the canton (referred to specifically as the "union") bearing fifty small, white, five-pointed stars. The 50 stars on the flag represent the 50 states of the United States of America, and the 13 stripes represent the thirteen British colonies that declared independence from the Kingdom of Great Britain, and became the first states in the U.S. The flag is often referred as The Star-Spangled Banner.
		</USA>

		<Russia>The flag was first used as an ensign for Russian merchant ships and later became official in 1696. It remained in use until the establishment of the Russian Socialist Federative Soviet Republic in 1917. During the Soviet Union's existence, it used the flag with the red field with the golden hammer and sickle and the golden bordered red star on top. With the dissolution of the Soviet Union, the former flag was eventually implemented again.
		</Russia>
	</Flag>

	<Landmark>
		<Algeria>
			<Marty surname="'s Memoria" city="Algiers" time="1982">An iconic concrete monument commemorating the Algerian war for independence. The monument was opened on the 20th anniversary of Algeria's independence (1962). It is fashioned in the shape of three standing palm leaves which shelter the "Eternal Flame" beneath. At the edge of each palm leaf stands a statue of a soldier, each representing a stage of Algeria's struggle.
			</Marty>
		</Algeria>

		<Australia>
			<Sydney surname="Opera House" city="Sydney" time="1973">One of the 20th century's most famous and distinctive buildings, this building is located in Sydney Harbour and host over 1500 performances annually
			</Sydney>
		</Australia>

		<Brazil>
			<Christ surname="the Redeemer" city="Rio de Janeiro" time="1931">The statue itself is 30 metres tall and is located in the top of the biggest mountain in Rio, the Corcovado. It was built with concrete and soapstone, by the Brazilian Engineer Heitor da Silva Costa and the French Sculptor Paul Landowski. The Christ is considered one of the new seven wonders of the world. 
			</Christ>
		</Brazil>

		<Canada>
			<CN surname="Tower" city="Toronto" time="1976">A concrete communications and observation tower in downtown Toronto. It held the record for the world's tallest free-standing structure for 32 years from 1975–2007 and was the world's tallest tower until 2009, being now the third tallest. Its name "CN" originally referred to Canadian National, the railway company that built the tower.
			</CN>
		</Canada>

		<China>
			<Great surname="Wall of China" city="Close to Beijing" time="Firstly built in the 7th century B.C">It is a series of fortifications made of stone, brick, tamped earth, wood, and other materials,  built across the historical northern borders of China to protect the Chinese states and empires against the raids and invasions of various nomadic groups. The walls were rebuilt and fortified several times, but the majority of what exists today was built during Ming Dinasty (1368-1644).
			</Great>
		</China>

		<Egypt>
			<Great surname="Sphinx" city="Giza" time="Approximately 2500 BC">The Sphinx is a mythical creature with the head of a human and the body of a lion. This statue measures 73 metres long and 20 metres high .It is believed that it was constructed in tribute to the Pharaoh Khafre and therefore the face of the sphinx would be a representation of the Pharaoh's face.
			</Great>
		</Egypt>

		<England>
			<Big surname="Ben" city="London" time="1859">Big Ben is the nickname for the Great Bell of the clock at the north end of the Palace of Westminster in London and is usually extended to refer to both the clock and the clock tower. The tower is officially Elizabeth Tower, renamed to celebrate the 60th anniversary of the accession of Queen Elizabeth II in 2012; until then, it was known simply as the Clock Tower.
			</Big>
		</England>

		<France>
			<Louvre surname="Museum" city="Paris" time="1793">It is the world's largest art museum, holding approximately 38,000 objects from prehistory to the 21st century, over an area of 72,735 square metres. Among so many famous art pieces, we can find the painting of one of the most famous women of the history. Maybe you've heard about her before... Mona Lisa!
			</Louvre>
		</France>

		<Germany>
			<Neuschwanstein surname="Castle" city="Hohenschwangau" time="1869">The palace was commissioned by Ludwig II of Bavaria. He paid for the palace out of his personal fortune and by means of extensive borrowing, rather than Bavarian public funds. The castle was intended as a home for the king, until he died in 1886. It was open to the public shortly after his death.
			</Neuschwanstein>
		</Germany>

		<Italy>
			<Coliseum city="Rome" time="80">The construction began under the emperor Vespasian in AD 72, and was completed in AD 80. It was used for gladiatorial contests and public spectacles such as animal hunts, executions and dramas based on Classical mythology. It's average audience was of around 65,000 spectators.
			</Coliseum>
		</Italy>

		<Portugal>
			<Pena surname="Palace" city="Sintra" time="1854">It is a Romanticist castle that stands on the top of a hill in the Sintra Mountains and can be seen from Lisbon. It was built by orders of the King Ferdinand II so it could be used as a summer residence for the Portuguese royal family. Nowadays, it is often used for state occasions by the President of the Portuguese Republic and other government officials.
			</Pena>
		</Portugal>

		<Spain>
			<Park surname="Güell" city="Barcelona" time="1914">It is a public park system composed of gardens and architectonic elements. The design of the park was made by Antoni Gaudí, a renowned Catalan Modernist architect. Gaudí used a lot of organic shapes and put into practice a series of innovative solutions for the buildings, making Park Güell a place ahead of its time in the 1910's.
			</Park>
		</Spain>

		<USA>
			<Statue surname="of Liberty" city="New York" time="1886">It is a neoclassical sculpture on Liberty Island in New York Harbor, made of copper, that France gave to the United States. The Statue of Liberty is a figure of a robed woman representing Libertas, a Roman goddess. She holds a torch above her head with her right hand, and in her left hand carries a tablet inscribed in Roman numerals with "July 4, 1776", the date of the U.S. Declaration of Independence. 
			</Statue>
		</USA>

		<Russia>
			<Saint surname="Basil's Cathedral" city="Moscow" time="1561">The building is located on the Red Square and was built by orders of Ivan the Terrible. It is shaped as a flame of a bonfire rising into the sky and has no analogues, in preceding, contemporary, or later architecture of Russia. Nowadays, after more than 450 years of its existence, the building is a museum.
			</Saint>
		</Russia>
	</Landmark>

	<Celebrity>
		<Algeria>
			<Souad surname="Massi">Souad Massi, born in 1972, is an Algerian singer, songwriter and guitarist. She began her career performing in the Kabyle political rock band Atakor, before leaving the country following a series of death threats. Lot of her music is a response to the rise of Islamic State, by providing a reminder of the creativity and tolerance of earlier Muslim civilisations, along with echoes of the idealism and anger that fuelled the Arab spring of 2010/11.
			</Souad>
		</Algeria>

		<Australia>
			<Hugh surname="Jackman">Hugh Jackman is an actor, singer, and producer. Jackman has won international recognition for his roles in a variety of film genres. He is mostly known for his long-running role as Wolverine in the X-Men film series.
			</Hugh>
		</Australia>

		<Brazil>
			<Carmen surname="Miranda" time="(1909-1955)">Carmen Miranda was actually born in Portugal, but came to Brazil by the age of one. She was responsible for inserting the country in the international showbiz scene, with which she worked for great part of her life. In the 40's, she was the most well-payed woman in the USA. She also had great influence in the rising of the Tropicalia, one of the most important Brazilian music movements.
			</Carmen>
		</Brazil>

		<Canada>
			<Jim surname="Carry">A Canadian actor, comedian, impressionist, screenwriter, and producer. He is known for his highly energetic and exaggerated performances. He performed in several well-known movies as Ace Ventura, Dumb and Dumber, The Truman Show, A Series of Unfortunate Events and Bruce Almighty.
			</Jim>
		</Canada>

		<China>
			<Bruce surname="Lee" time="(1940-1973)">Bruce Lee was a Hong Kong and American actor, film director, martial artist, martial arts instructor, philosopher and founder of the martial art Jeet Kune Do one of the kungfu styles. He is widely considered to be one of the most influential martial artists of all time, and a pop culture icon of the 20th century. He is often credited with helping to change the way Asians were presented in American films.
			</Bruce>
		</China>

		<Egypt>
			<Anwar surname="Sadat" time="(1918-1981)">He was the third President of Egypt, serving from 1970 until his assassination by fundamentalist army officers on 1981. He led Egypt in the Yom Kippur War of 1973 to regain Egypt's Sinai Peninsula, which Israel had occupied since the Six-Day War of 1967, making him a hero in Egypt. Afterwards, he engaged in negotiations with Israel, culminating in the Egypt–Israel Peace Treaty, which made him won the Nobel Peace Prize.
			</Anwar>
		</Egypt>

		<England>
			<Adele>Adele is an English singer and songwriter. After graduating from the BRIT School for Performing Arts and Technology in 2006, Adele was given a recording contract after a friend posted her demo on Myspace the same year. Since then, Adele has been writting notorious songs as Someone Like You, Hello, Rolling in the Deep and Send My Love.
			</Adele>
		</England>

		<France>
			<Coco surname="Chanel" time="(1883-1971)">She was a French fashion designer and businesswoman. She was the founder and namesake of the Chanel brand. Along with Paul Poiret, Chanel was credited in the post-World War I era with liberating women from the constraints of the "corseted silhouette" and popularizing a sporty, casual chic as the feminine standard of style.
			</Coco>
		</France>

		<Germany>
			<Angela surname="Merkel">She is a German politician serving as Chancellor of Germany since 2005 and leader of the centre-right Christian Democratic Union (CDU) since 2000. Merkel has been widely described as the leader of the European Union in practice, and the most powerful woman in the world.
			</Angela>
		</Germany>

		<Italy>
			<Grazia surname="Deledda " time="(1871-1936)">Grazia Deledda was an Italian writer who won the Nobel Prize for Literature in 1926 and one of the leading figures of the verism movement in literature. She brought out the dialect of her region elevating it from the domestic sphere to the level of literature and in such contributed to the evolution of the Italian literature and language.
			</Grazia>
		</Italy>

		<Portugal>
			<Cristiano surname="Ronaldo">He is a professional footballer who plays as a forward for Spanish club Real Madrid and the Portugal national team. Often considered the best player in the world and widely regarded as one of the greatest of all time, Ronaldo has four FIFA Ballon d'Or awards, the most for a European player, and is the first player in history to win four European Golden Shoes.
			</Cristiano>
		</Portugal>

		<Spain>
			<Antonio surname="Banderas">An actor, director, singer, and producer. Banderas began his acting career with a series of films by director Pedro Almodóvar and then appeared in high-profile Hollywood movies, especially in the 1990s, including Interview with the Vampire, The Mask of Zorro, The Expendables 3 and Spy Kids. 
			</Antonio>
		</Spain>

		<USA>
			<Jimi surname="Hendrix" time="(1942-1970)">Jimi Hendrix was an rock guitarist, singer, and songwriter. Although his mainstream career spanned only four years, he is widely regarded as one of the most notorius electric guitarists in the history, being one of the most influent Psychedelic Rock musician of all times. Poor Hendrix died at the age of 27, but he is still rocking around the world!
			</Jimi>
		</USA>

		<Russia>
			<Vladimir surname="Putin">He is a Russian statesman serving as President of the Russian Federation since 7 May 2012. He was Prime Minister of the Russian Federation from 1999 until 2000, and again from 2008 until 2012. Anthough Under Putin's leadershipthe Russian economy grew for eight straight years, Russia has also scored poorly in Transparency International's Corruption Perceptions Index and thus Experts no longer consider Russia a democracy.
			</Vladimir>
		</Russia>
	</Celebrity>
</Topic>
